Mikheil Ispiriani

Tbilisi Georgia

+995-599-176-887 | mikheilispiriani@yahoo.com | https://github.com/mikhita | https://www.linkedin.com/in/mikheil-ispiryan-1a00b8231/l

Personal Profile

Hello, I'm Misha! My first steps in web development was The CodeHS Introduction to Programming with Karel the Dog course, where I learn the basics of programming in JavaScript, from that moment around 1 year ago I fell in love with super intensive thinking and codding. Nowadays I am too much Eager to learn something new and interesting for me in the programming and I am ready for new challenges. I'm passionate about software development and I'm skilledin MARKup(super-responsive), JavaScript and React. I'm now looking for a junior developer position as I learned how to code at super-intensiveBootcamp 'BitcampPro'.

Education

Fullstack Codding "BitCamp"

Tbilisi, Georgia(country)

Software Engineering Program

June 2022 - Current

- Impressive Training Program With An Emphasis On Fullstack Web Development
- Full React Course
- Full Responsive Design MarkUp Course
- Full Javascript Course
- Basics of Back End Development and APIs
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data structure

FreeCodeCamp United States

Donor-supported tax-exempt nonprofit organization

May 2021 - current

August 2022 - current

- Responsive Web Design Certification
- Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures Certificate
- Front End Development Libraries Certificate

Work Experience

Frontend Mentor United States

Web Developer

• I take Challenges From Frontend Mentor, that provides designs so that you can practice your front-end skills using a real-life workflow. Challenges include designs (both mobile and desktop), assets, and a style guide to get you started.

Codding "BitCamp"

Tbilisi Georgia(Country)

Tutor August 2022 - current

• I am helping Students who wants to learn programming to solve tasks which needs to have nice experience in responsive design.

Codding "BitCamp" Projects ____

Fullstack Web Development Codding "BitCamp"

Tbilisi, Georgia (country)

Codding "BitCamp"

June 2022 - current

- My github pages link: https://github.com/mikhita
- Here is my portfolio Website: https://github.com/mikhita/My-portfolio/deployments
- I learn the most part of Javascript with Interactive comments section project: https://github.com/mikhita/interactive-comments-section/deployments
- This project of tips calculator helps me to learn a lot about Javascript: https://mikhita.github.io/tips-calculator-frontend-mentors/
- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TailWind, React, Responsive Design, Mongodb, Express, postman, mySQL, JSON, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Axios, Joi, Redux, Multer and etc...
- Soft Skills: Time Management, Teamwork, Presentation skills, Report writing.

Languages ____

English Pre-Intermediate proficiency

Russian Professional proficiency
Georgian Native proficiency

Armenian Only for speaking proficiency